{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fc9ff124495ad891d6f"},"product_asin":"B0744GC2CK","QAs":[{"question":"Can I use the serum everyday ??","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"PADMAJA NAIR","date":"2022-08-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use the mask everyday?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"PADMAJA NAIR","date":"2022-08-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its best for colourd hair?","answer":"Well I dont have coloured hair so can’t say exactly. But its good overall. For coloured hair Xtenso version is better I think!","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj_n_Boo","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya ye sulphate free hai","answer":"Yes sulphate free","votes":"0","username":"lynette righton","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this product for keratin treated hair","answer":"Well it is a mild shampoo. Best for all hair types especially for dry and damaged hair. Specifically it is not recommended for any type of treated hair but I don’t think it will do any harm. It is quite mild","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj_n_Boo","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good for coloured hair?","answer":"yes it is","votes":"0","username":"PADMAJA NAIR","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is absolute loreal shampoo is sulphate free?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"PADMAJA NAIR","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I use this shampoo for smoothening hair?","answer":"Its for repair contorl of your hair damage , i have been using it for about 18 months or so , i find that hair is not frizzy after use , and they do have a smoothe look and feel. if that's what you are trying to ask. if you are refrring to smoothening as straightening , then no , this shampoo will not do that","votes":"0","username":"MastiSingh","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fcbff124495ad891d7e"},"product_asin":"B08CSHBPD5","QAs":[{"question":"Seram is oil","answer":"no, its not oil actually","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-08-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"At 712 price shampoo + conditioner and serum  you are giving or only shampoo and conditioner","answer":"plz contact dealer","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-08-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"1l(pake of 5) means total 5l","answer":"No its only 1 l and its associated sub items but idint receive those.better to don't buy this.","votes":"0","username":"Sreenivasulu Donka","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"1l pack of 5 it means 5pack 1liter each total 5ltr right?","answer":"Yes, videos get shared after due quality check by Amazon team. Mine got posted!","votes":"0","username":"Saral Srivastava","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many shampoo bottles comes in pack of 5?","answer":"1","votes":"0","username":"MANISH SAINI","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product is only for women ?","answer":"It can use man too","votes":"0","username":"Aayush Lohar","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"1l (pack of 5) does that mean total we will get 5l shampoo?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Din't get my product but it is showing in my order that product has been delivered what is this ?","answer":"talk to amazon customer care","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-08-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"What does pack of  5 mean ?","answer":"5 nos","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get the product without packet or sealed bag? I received the loose bottles today,not packed.I doubt if it's original","answer":"Of course original","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it also work on oiled hair?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Chandan R.","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we apply oil when your are use loarel shampoo","answer":"Well honestly speaking this depends on your hair nature, if ur scalp becomes too much dry after shampoo then u should apply a better hair oil. For more, u should consult a hair expert","votes":"0","username":"MANISH SAINI","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Were is my order","answer":"Yes little apply oil and 1hour after wash the hair","votes":"0","username":"Nita d.","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fd1ff124495ad891d9b"},"product_asin":"B08CSFFD26","QAs":[{"question":"Is it paraben free or not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mrinmay haldar","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fd1ff124495ad891d9d"},"product_asin":"B08T2Y2Q4T","QAs":[{"question":"Is this good for post smoothening care??","answer":"Yes is good for smoothening care","votes":"0","username":"Kadipakam Triveni","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this shampoo prevents hairfall??","answer":"Its fake shampoo with no smell. Weird liquid. Dont buy.","votes":"0","username":"Sheetz","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can 7 years girl use it?","answer":"No. Its fake. Dont buy","votes":"0","username":"Sheetz","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this leave-in cream used for protecting hair from blow drying and hair straightening  heat?","answer":"Yes this leave in Cream is awesome product","votes":"0","username":"Kadipakam Triveni","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"which day my order come","answer":"not good. there is side effcates hairfall","votes":"0","username":"shamsher singh","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does hair growth","answer":"Yes perfect shampoo for hair growth","votes":"0","username":"Kadipakam Triveni","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"It will make hair stronger","answer":"very bad product don't buy","votes":"0","username":"shamsher singh","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fd2ff124495ad891da7"},"product_asin":"B006LXAG4K","QAs":[{"question":"Does it come with a conditioner?","answer":"No, it doesn't.","votes":"0","username":"Kalyan N.","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date ?","answer":"3 years from date of manufacture.","votes":"0","username":"anbarasu","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fd6ff124495ad891db7"},"product_asin":"B008KH5U28","QAs":[{"question":"What about expiry date ?","answer":"That’s a perfect question…… you will get sufficient shelf life of the product. Go ahead","votes":"0","username":"Satyarth","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fd6ff124495ad891db9"},"product_asin":"B08DP1NJN5","QAs":[{"question":"can both boys and girls use the hair color","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Panchali Sen","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fd9ff124495ad891dc0"},"product_asin":"B07J68V1MG","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date of both products??","answer":"Dear Meenakshi,The Manufacturing date & Expiry date of the products are mentioned on the product packs. Presently, Cloudtail India and RK World Info Comm are associated sellers on Amazon, and L’Oréal Paris products purchased through them would be authentic. You may contact the above sellers to get the details, before placing your order.see less","votes":"0","username":"Customer Care","date":"2022-08-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fdaff124495ad891dc6"},"product_asin":"B084MJPK42","QAs":[{"question":"is it sulfate free?","answer":"No, its not.","votes":"0","username":"Tanya Sahay","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fdaff124495ad891dc8"},"product_asin":"B07MW4ZRJL","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be used on colored hair?","answer":"I color my hair and I use the shampoo. It is sulfate free.","votes":"0","username":"SMi","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fdbff124495ad891dcc"},"product_asin":"B092566RWC","QAs":[{"question":"Is item will come full or empty","answer":"They are full","votes":"0","username":"Gayatri","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it original loreal???","answer":"Yeah I think so","votes":"0","username":"Gayatri","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fdcff124495ad891dd1"},"product_asin":"B0744KHS4K","QAs":[{"question":"Does this shampoo gives volume to the hair?","answer":"I have used L'Oréal Professionnel Serie Expert Density Advanced Shampoo for quite some time, and I would recommend it to anybody looking for increased volume for their hair. This shampoo also had made my hair feel very soft and manageable.","votes":"0","username":"Bidushini","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"for  this shampoo !! can i use this l'oréal paris anti-hair fall conditioner, reinforcing & nourishing for hair growth ??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"jay  patel","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the expiry date?","answer":"2years","votes":"0","username":"jay  patel","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it with st botanica biotin conditioner?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"jay  patel","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is bottle model changed? I got different shape bottle.","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"jay  patel","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fdeff124495ad891ddf"},"product_asin":"B076CH85SL","QAs":[{"question":"Does this helps to stimulate lengthy hair","answer":"No.. Mine is dry and frizzy hair, this just helps to make a bit easy to manage..","votes":"0","username":"Surekha","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fe1ff124495ad891deb"},"product_asin":"B0B9RCCV48","QAs":[{"question":"How Many days once we can use this?","answer":"I used it every day","votes":"0","username":"kavita","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is sulphate and paraben free?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"kavita","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fe4ff124495ad891df1"},"product_asin":"B06Y3WVH2X","QAs":[{"question":"Can this shampoo be used on Inoa colored hair?","answer":"Yes!!","votes":"0","username":"sonu.mahtani","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fe5ff124495ad891df8"},"product_asin":"B08RZVDQN9","QAs":[{"question":"Does this work for frizzy hair as well?","answer":"This has to used after professional hair Smoothening treatment to keep your hair smooth and straight.","votes":"0","username":"Sushilkumar S Mundhe","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fe9ff124495ad891e08"},"product_asin":"B09QBV3P1G","QAs":[{"question":"Is it suitable for oily scalp?","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"Sonal Indora","date":"2022-08-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is for anti Hair fall??","answer":"I am having dry scalp for which it is very good but for anti hair fall I can't say anything?","votes":"0","username":"Aarti Tyagi","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is is suitable for men?","answer":"It suited my husband so yes.","votes":"0","username":"Pankhuri","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is really chemicals free","answer":"Yes it is...it really helped my hair trust me!!!","votes":"0","username":"Amazon customer…","date":"2022-08-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it removes oil from scalp?","answer":"Yes it removes oil from the scalp","votes":"0","username":"Shalini Chandirasekaran","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"This sampoo is suitable for all hair types","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Neha","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is is good for keratin treated hair ?","answer":"Yes this is sulphate free","votes":"0","username":"Neha","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fe9ff124495ad891e12"},"product_asin":"B07HB2L7QD","QAs":[{"question":"Present product expiry date","answer":"Expiry is in - September 2023","votes":"0","username":"m2r Mart's Bucket 🛒","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fe9ff124495ad891e14"},"product_asin":"B07HB4FKZS","QAs":[{"question":"Dove saimpo 650ml.ki expire date show nahin horahi h","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-08-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date","answer":"Its 12/23","votes":"0","username":"Waseem ahmad","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"I am 12 years old can I use it?","answer":"Absolutely!!","votes":"0","username":"Waseem ahmad","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it sulphate and paraban free shampoo","answer":"Yes it's free","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gst credit is applicable?","answer":"No since you are the final consumer","votes":"0","username":"Waseem ahmad","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066febff124495ad891e1e"},"product_asin":"B07H9T25WH","QAs":[{"question":"Expire date","answer":"Expiry date of product 10/2023","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date please","answer":"Expiry date of product 10/2023","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date plzzz","answer":"January 25","votes":"0","username":"Ramchandra","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date  of this product?","answer":"Its such a great with regionable price","votes":"0","username":"Sachin","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expery date","answer":"January 25","votes":"0","username":"Ramchandra","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of the product","answer":"Expiry date is 09/2023. MFD is 10/2021.","votes":"0","username":"ANIRBAN CHAKRABORTY","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Expiry date.?","answer":"January 25","votes":"0","username":"Ramchandra","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066febff124495ad891e26"},"product_asin":"B017BFNGLG","QAs":[{"question":"Ek paiket me kitna sampoo hai?","answer":"I didn't count but more than 30","votes":"0","username":"Srilakshmi vattikuti","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fecff124495ad891e28"},"product_asin":"B09QC4BM5M","QAs":[{"question":"Can i use this after keratin treatment?","answer":"I don't like this product 😏","votes":"0","username":"Amu","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fecff124495ad891e2c"},"product_asin":"B07H9SV624","QAs":[{"question":"What is manufacturing date ?","answer":"Manufacturing date is 09/21","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product expiry date","answer":"07/23","votes":"0","username":"Public","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry day as on 15 july 2022 ?","answer":"07-21  to  06-23","votes":"0","username":"Mohan","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of this product","answer":"06-23","votes":"0","username":"Mohan","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the latest mfd of this product for purchases in july 2022?","answer":"i brought it before 2 months its mfd is 08/2021","votes":"0","username":"Public","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date of shampoo","answer":"07/2021@06/2023","votes":"0","username":"Mohan","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"7/23","votes":"0","username":"Public","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fefff124495ad891e38"},"product_asin":"B00CQ41JE4","QAs":[{"question":"Mfg and expiry date of the product?","answer":"11/22","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Babu G","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fefff124495ad891e3d"},"product_asin":"B093SXXN5V","QAs":[{"question":"I want Manufacturing date","answer":"05/22","votes":"0","username":"Sohan Parakash Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expirey date plz ?","answer":"I bought it few months ago.","votes":"0","username":"Wahida bano","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the color of shampoo?","answer":"Cream colour,","votes":"0","username":"Wahida bano","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"It will be mentioned on product,","votes":"0","username":"Wahida bano","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"04/24","votes":"0","username":"Sohan Parakash Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Show expire date ???","answer":"04/24","votes":"0","username":"Sohan Parakash Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Show expire date on product...","answer":"04/24","votes":"0","username":"Sohan Parakash Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date pls??","answer":"04/24","votes":"0","username":"Sohan Parakash Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expery date","answer":"04/24","votes":"0","username":"Sohan Parakash Srivastava","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066ff1ff124495ad891e4d"},"product_asin":"B07H9SV61Y","QAs":[{"question":"What is expirey date of this shampoo","answer":"No current date","votes":"0","username":"Yeasin Gaji","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066ff2ff124495ad891e54"},"product_asin":"B00QKAQN3M","QAs":[{"question":"Exp date?","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date at this time ?","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066ff8ff124495ad891e64"},"product_asin":"B074ZCKWSN","QAs":[{"question":"Can teenage girls use it ?","answer":"Absolutely! I've used it since my teen days and am still continuing to use this. It's the most budget friendly option for frizzy hair.","votes":"0","username":"Remi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"My hairs are not keratin but i want to use this shampoo to get rid of hairfall amd frizzy hairs, will it be okay to use?","answer":"It'll perfectly work fine for your frizzy hair. Hair fall can be less if you keep a regular wash cycle of once in every 2-3 days, but apply anti hairfall oil for your issues","votes":"0","username":"Remi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Instead of tresemme keretain smooth shampoo Which medicated shampoos should i use  which suit my hairs for hairfall dandruff and hair whitening","answer":"Selsun is a medicated shampoo for dandruff. Works best.","votes":"0","username":"Remi","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066ffbff124495ad891e70"},"product_asin":"B088CGPPC5","QAs":[{"question":"Does it works on dry scalp?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066ffbff124495ad891e74"},"product_asin":"B07L3YNL2V","QAs":[{"question":"Expired date","answer":"06/23","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expire date","answer":"Every product has a separate expiry date.","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Saini","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066ffeff124495ad891e81"},"product_asin":"B088CCYM9D","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be used for keratin treated hair?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is mantain my keratin treatment hair?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can used this shampoo for permanent hair straighening and keratin treatment?","answer":"Yez","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it on post nanoplastia","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why delivery not happening in any location in India, not even in metro cities.","answer":"It is happening now","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this shampoo paraben and sulphate free both ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fffff124495ad891e89"},"product_asin":"B07F2QCLP2","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date???","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63066fffff124495ad891e8d"},"product_asin":"B07L3ZCJ53","QAs":[{"question":"When is the expiry date of this product?","answer":"9/23","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this shampoo  & conditioner after aqua treatment??","answer":"This product makes your hair shine and imparts silkiness.","votes":"0","username":"Payal Pal","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expired date is aug 23?","answer":"Yes, you are correct.","votes":"0","username":"shekhar","date":"2022-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of this shampoo bottle?","answer":"09/2023","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is work on Curly hair","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"irfan boghani","date":"2022-08-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiring date","answer":"09/23","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Expiring date","answer":"Exp Date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of this bottle","answer":"Exp Date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"X expiry date kab hai","answer":"Exp date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Today i will purchase this product what expected expiry date","answer":"Expiry date :- 09/23","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date ??","answer":"No expiration. Use it.","votes":"0","username":"S M Hussain","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expired date","answer":"Exp date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Plz let me know expiry of this product?","answer":"Exp date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of this shampoo bottle?","answer":"Exp date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of this product?","answer":"I have used this up and don't have details but it's quite sufficient.","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date ...?","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"9/23","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date?","answer":"Exp date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expired date","answer":"09/2023","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you please tell me the expiry date?","answer":"march2023","votes":"0","username":"irfan boghani","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many months does 1 litre bottle can be used","answer":"Exp date 09/2023","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date kitna hai","answer":"September 2023","votes":"0","username":"Kishori Prabhu","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it pro collection shampoo","answer":"Yes it is...i Found Tresemme Antihairfall is 10× better than this...","votes":"0","username":"Neha dixit","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for Male?","answer":"Male and female both can use it","votes":"0","username":"RAJA MUKHOPADHYAY","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date ?","answer":"24 month","votes":"0","username":"Deepak Katara","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is ka use date kya hai","answer":"April 2024","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Rai","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is ka use dae kya hai","answer":"April 2024","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Rai","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of the product","answer":"April 2024","votes":"0","username":"Bittu Rai","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Explain expiring date ?","answer":"It's good product","votes":"0","username":"irfan boghani","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mfg and expiry date","answer":"MFG: MAR 2022","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date??","answer":"May 2023","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Barman","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date for now","answer":"It depends","votes":"0","username":"Mani","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why don't you guys give the details of production date and expiry date of the product.","answer":"It's different for different products","votes":"0","username":"Mani","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date for current order?","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expired date of this product?","answer":"9/23.","votes":"0","username":"Kishori Prabhu","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expirey date","answer":"9/23. Or September 2023.","votes":"0","username":"Kishori Prabhu","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi everyone, Does it control hair fall really?? There are some mixed reviews pls advise is it good to buy??","answer":"No,It doesn't control your hairfall","votes":"0","username":"master mandol","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"Nov 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tressme good for damage hair","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Varsha","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067001ff124495ad891e9a"},"product_asin":"B07FHD9Y8M","QAs":[{"question":"Is this shampoo makes hair longer faster ?","answer":"This is the worst shampoo I ever used. Lots of chemicals increase your hair fall faster.","votes":"0","username":"Premlata S.","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067002ff124495ad891ea0"},"product_asin":"B07F2ZXJN7","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have conditioner with shampoo?","answer":"No, only shampoo 🧴","votes":"0","username":"S M Hussain","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please tell expiry date","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Use by date","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Use by","answer":"Nice product thank you Amazon,,😊","votes":"0","username":"Jadav sejal ☺️","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date ?","answer":"Nov 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Eski mfd or expires date kya hai","answer":"Exp Nov 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"Its good","votes":"0","username":"sangeeta rajput","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"Nov 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this for low porosity hair?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067003ff124495ad891eaa"},"product_asin":"B018U1F668","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date of this sampooo..","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date of this product","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it chemical free...like sulphate ?????","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of this product??","answer":"NOV 2024","votes":"0","username":"Castle Creek International","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"When this item is manufactured","answer":"Amazon marketplace gives recently manufactured products. 1 to 2 months maximum old.","votes":"0","username":"Prof. K Bhowmick","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it remove dandruff","answer":"Various variety of the shampoo are available, you can try the dandruff control variety of the shampoo.","votes":"0","username":"Prof. K Bhowmick","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067004ff124495ad891ec2"},"product_asin":"B07J5NLHWW","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"No mentioned expire date","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date of this product??","answer":"No mentioned expiry date","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067007ff124495ad891ed6"},"product_asin":"B07YWMQHYJ","QAs":[{"question":"Why does it make the  hair very dry & frizzy??","answer":"No make the hair seelky and smooth","votes":"0","username":"shailendra singh","date":"2022-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the chemicals in the lotion base you have?","answer":"Same chemical of which your body is made of.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Expiry date of this product ?","answer":"2025","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference Bio neem vs Fresh neem?","answer":"Nothing","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"As the label says shampoo with conditioner then does it needs to be conditioned again?","answer":"You can if you want to but you don't need","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"It make  is for curly hair","answer":"It is made for all kinds of hair","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306700aff124495ad891ef0"},"product_asin":"B08JR4RHCX","QAs":[{"question":"After using this shampoo, which conditioner have to use?","answer":"I will suggest any banana conditioner. In my case, I use The Body Shop Banana conditioner but since that could be expensive, I think you should go for Tresemme, Mamaearth hair conditioners. If you have dry hair Banana conditioner is best. But if you are looking for budget friendly conditioner you can choose Tresemme.","votes":"0","username":"Vatsla","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good for splits end?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vatsla","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306700cff124495ad891ef6"},"product_asin":"B07YWMQRNJ","QAs":[{"question":"It contains sulphate?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"sairamcharan","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306700cff124495ad891ef9"},"product_asin":"B07YWNMLWX","QAs":[{"question":"Is it suitable for oily scalp?","answer":"Yea I have oily scalp and it works well for me.","votes":"0","username":"Sandhya Gadicherla","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306700eff124495ad891f02"},"product_asin":"B07YWMQRPH","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date of biotek henna leaf","answer":"36 months from the date of manufacture","votes":"0","username":"sree ambica","date":"2022-07-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306700fff124495ad891f04"},"product_asin":"B00791CV8C","QAs":[{"question":"Does this shampoo add volume to the hair for boys?","answer":"Yes, but you have to use walnut conditioner too with this shampoo.","votes":"0","username":"AMAR KUMAR","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"can boys apply this shampoo","answer":"Yes, boys can use this shampoo. I am using it","votes":"0","username":"Prashanth","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067013ff124495ad891f14"},"product_asin":"B07YWNQPWB","QAs":[{"question":"Is this shampoo paraben and sulphate free.","answer":"Yes, as per biotique and amazon website description","votes":"0","username":"YOGESH M","date":"2022-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I an 13 year old and my hairtype is b , i dont have habit of using conditioner, will it get my hair dry , cause iam facing hairproblems theese days ?","answer":"Contents must be suit ur hair and skin type.. Take ayurvedic dr opinion 1st..","votes":"0","username":"YOGESH M","date":"2022-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why only 10 % ingredients mentioned??","answer":"its in proportionate .. the same has been done after proper research and study.. if not ..then product might be turn into toilet cleaner..","votes":"0","username":"YOGESH M","date":"2022-08-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067015ff124495ad891f1c"},"product_asin":"B07YWNQPWM","QAs":[{"question":"Can this shampoo stop hair falling?","answer":"Oh no oh no ..no no no no no no 😀","votes":"0","username":"master mandol","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067017ff124495ad891f24"},"product_asin":"B07WQJBPZC","QAs":[{"question":"30 watts adaptor will this fit ?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"dhaval deshmukh","date":"2022-08-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible with ipad pro 12.9\" 2nd gen?","answer":"yes it can fit","votes":"0","username":"dhaval deshmukh","date":"2022-08-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work with apple 12w (a1401) ipad adapter? Anyone please reply","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"R C Srimal","date":"2022-08-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it Compatible with a1540?","answer":"yes will all apple mac ipad adaptors","votes":"0","username":"HOUSE_OF_BRANDS","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it support MacBook air m1?","answer":"yes suitabe with all apple mac ipad adaptors","votes":"0","username":"HOUSE_OF_BRANDS","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this compatible with A2338? Macbook pro 2020","answer":"yes suitabe with all apple mac ipad adaptors","votes":"0","username":"HOUSE_OF_BRANDS","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067018ff124495ad891f2c"},"product_asin":"B09GY32G62","QAs":[{"question":"Is this pack of 4 or 3?","answer":"Pack of 4","votes":"0","username":"AADISHWAR CREATIONS","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which cloth is this","answer":"It's cotton. I'm using this daily as handkerchief & occasionally as Bandana too.","votes":"0","username":"Rupak Choudhury","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's has Double side printed","answer":"No single side.","votes":"0","username":"ME ONLINE STORE 24 X 7","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"The colour will fade or not?","answer":"Vaise toh nahi hota. AaDhoop main nahi sukana","votes":"0","username":"AADISHWAR CREATIONS","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067019ff124495ad891f35"},"product_asin":"B077P1B5X4","QAs":[{"question":"What is the date of expiry in head and shoulder cool menthol shampoo","answer":"2024","votes":"0","username":"Kumar","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is mfg date of this product","answer":"Life time","votes":"0","username":"Jay","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Q:What is the expiry date now?","answer":"Hi as I purchased the manufactured date mentioned as 03/22 Indicate: Use before 36 months from date of manufacture...","votes":"0","username":"Prasanna.SSK","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067019ff124495ad891f39"},"product_asin":"B074ZF7PVZ","QAs":[{"question":"Is it USB headset","answer":"Nope. It's 3.5MM jack.","votes":"0","username":"Gyandip Deka","date":"2022-08-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I was brought this headphone on jan 2022..my mike is not working properly now. i have 1 year warranty. so i want replacement.","answer":"You can replace it. You'll have to go on official website and register your complaint.","votes":"0","username":"Vedant P.","date":"2022-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compatible for realme7 ??","answer":"If it has 3.5 jack then yes","votes":"0","username":"Akshay j.","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get in 1 rupee","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Lakshay Kumar","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this look good when you wear it","answer":"Absolutely. No doubt in it. It looks cool when you wear it.","votes":"0","username":"pradeep ram s","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you sell spare cushions for Boat bass 900 headphones","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Jain","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"how it connects to professional headphone port","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Debanjan Ukil","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what type of Conection 6.5mm adapter?","answer":"Take connector","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Jain","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim Warranty within warranty period?","answer":"Dtls Already given there","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Jain","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to get warrenty replacement","answer":"Call customer care service","votes":"0","username":"Pawan Jain","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it work on starmaker app with clarity?","answer":"Yes sure","votes":"0","username":"Bhupendra P.","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to adjust the headphones to fit?","answer":"Just plug properly then start","votes":"0","username":"Bhupendra P.","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the impedance and cable length?","answer":"32om 1.5 meter cable length","votes":"0","username":"Bhupendra P.","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067019ff124495ad891f44"},"product_asin":"B0B293BVRT","QAs":[{"question":"Is this used to cover our ear for restrict from cold air","answer":"Nope...The purpose of this headband is to absorb the sweat during your workouts/fitness routines.","votes":"0","username":"ABHISHEK GOEL","date":"2022-08-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701aff124495ad891f4a"},"product_asin":"B07P21CHH8","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date??","answer":"Far away from purchasing date","votes":"0","username":"Azzu","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701aff124495ad891f4d"},"product_asin":"B09G6T3JDK","QAs":[{"question":"Whether it is compatible with oral b braun","answer":"Yes. I have been using with it","votes":"0","username":"Anandineelu…","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it fit to the oral b star war edition kids toothbrush?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Inrali","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701bff124495ad891f55"},"product_asin":"B00C9TT7AY","QAs":[{"question":"Can this be used with lifelong lldc18 electric toothbrush?","answer":"Life long I can't assure u but u can use for few years with replacement of brushing heads.","votes":"0","username":"Sanath Kumar","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Head change time?","answer":"Just takes few minutes, including cleaning after removal of old Toothbrush head.","votes":"0","username":"KHIZAR ALI KHAN","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is that washebal ??","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"Lakshmi Raman","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Oral-b pro-expert ortho orthodontic 35 soft toothbrush, assorted colors https://www.amazon.ae/dp/b001nzamju/ref=cm_sw_r_apan_i_b3262na3ecwnz6yvqwh9","answer":"How and the way you use it","votes":"0","username":"Om Parkash","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to fix and how to use, where we put cell","answer":"Cell it will be there just press and use.. it will be at the bottom of the brush","votes":"0","username":"Sanath Kumar","date":"2022-08-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701cff124495ad891f5b"},"product_asin":"B082YYVTWX","QAs":[{"question":"There is no warranty card user manuel enclosed..should i return it??","answer":"Hello !","votes":"0","username":"Caresmith India","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is brush head available from special space odyssey edition?","answer":"Please do not buy this brush if your teeth are sensitive","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"The description says 2 heads, 1 soft and 1 medium. Can i get both medium heads instead of soft","answer":"Hello !","votes":"0","username":"Caresmith India","date":"2022-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Charging cable is micro usb or type C ?","answer":"Caresmith SPARK Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush comes with Micro USB Charging cable.","votes":"0","username":"Caresmith India","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Medium replacement head available?","answer":"2 nos along with brush","votes":"0","username":"Krishna","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the weight of this brush? I think it's wrongly mentioned 1.4 kg in the description... Or is it actually heavy?","answer":"Weight of the Spark electric rechargeable toothbrush is 150 g","votes":"0","username":"Caresmith India","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which model I should buy for my 11 year old son? Kid or Adult?","answer":"The brush has soft bristles so adult one will work just fine","votes":"0","username":"Amit Singh","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compitable with spark one electric battery toothbrush?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Shaji","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use Agaro brush heads for this toothbrush?","answer":"Agaro brush heads may not be compatible with Spark electric toothbrush.","votes":"0","username":"Caresmith India","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701dff124495ad891f6a"},"product_asin":"B00PBGPVAM","QAs":[{"question":"Is it compatible with Braun Oral-B professional care electric toothbrush?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"KAKU RATHORE","date":"2022-08-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it compatible to Oral B Pro 2 2000 ???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"KAKU RATHORE","date":"2022-08-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get charging cable with brush","answer":"No only the 2 brushes.","votes":"0","username":"Mohteshim khan","date":"2022-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"When will this be back in stock?","answer":"yes charging cable with brush","votes":"0","username":"KAKU RATHORE","date":"2022-08-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701dff124495ad891f6d"},"product_asin":"B08KHZH344","QAs":[{"question":"Does this shampoo remove dandruff","answer":"Not at all","votes":"0","username":"LALIT KUMAR","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Would like to know the expiry date of the shampoo as well as manufacture date","answer":"Not available","votes":"0","username":"LALIT KUMAR","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701fff124495ad891f72"},"product_asin":"B01EJIEC8O","QAs":[{"question":"Current manufacturing date ?","answer":"feburuary 2022","votes":"0","username":"Ashirwad seller","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":": Current manufacturin : Current manufacturing date and validity?","answer":"02/2022","votes":"0","username":"Ashirwad seller","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701fff124495ad891f75"},"product_asin":"B00ENZRLRS","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"36 Months {3 Years } from the DATE OF MANUFATURE. Look at the label printed on the bottle for the Manufactured date..","votes":"0","username":"Bob","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is manufacturing date?","answer":"Sep 2021","votes":"0","username":"Nitish","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the manufacturing date","answer":"The date it was packed","votes":"0","username":"simarjit","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date kya h?","answer":"Its 36 months from date of manufacture. Although you get the latest manufactured dated product.","votes":"0","username":"Thirumalesh K","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is mfg and expiry date latest by June 2022?","answer":"Mfg stands for manufacturing and its 36 months from manufactured date on the product.","votes":"0","username":"Thirumalesh K","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Latest Mfg and expiry date ?","answer":"Mfg date 4/2022","votes":"0","username":"Kashish khilwani","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expire date","answer":"2024","votes":"0","username":"Nitish","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date?","answer":"The expire date is 36 months from the manufactured date it almost 3years of expire date.","votes":"0","username":"Thirumalesh K","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing date and expiry date now??","answer":"The date on which the product is manufactured from the factory and it goes 36 months from manufactured date as expire date.","votes":"0","username":"Thirumalesh K","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6306701fff124495ad891f7f"},"product_asin":"B077P66WKX","QAs":[{"question":"Is it for male or female?","answer":"It's a unisex shampoo bro.","votes":"0","username":"Obang","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it good for smoothened hair","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gaurav jain","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067020ff124495ad891f86"},"product_asin":"B00ENZRCBI","QAs":[{"question":"Ex date","answer":"Ex date in 2025","votes":"0","username":"Ashirwad seller","date":"2022-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Date of manufacturing?","answer":"09/21","votes":"0","username":"Mahila Udan Kendra","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067022ff124495ad891f8c"},"product_asin":"B07MWH55SV","QAs":[{"question":"Will it fit proclinic 250r","answer":"Hi Subash, we're glad to know your interest in our product. Colgate ProClinical Replaceable Brush Heads fits every Colgate ProClinical electric toothbrush model. Hope this helps clarify. Many thanks!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-08-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this work with Colgate hum?","answer":"Hi Shahnawaz , this replaceable head cannot be used with the product you're referring to. It fits any of the Colgate Proclinical Electric Toothbrushes. Hope this helps. Thanks for checking in!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use for Gleem rechargeable tooth brush ?","answer":"Hi Amazon Customer, Gleem is not of Colgate. You can use Colgate Rechargeable toothbrush heads with all type Colgate Pro Clinical electric toothbrush model. Hope this helps clarify. Many thanks!","votes":"0","username":"A manufacturer","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067023ff124495ad891f94"},"product_asin":"B081X55K5F","QAs":[{"question":"Does it fit with health scence electric toothbrush","answer":"Yes it fits","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh Bajaj","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it fit on Oral b cross brush ?","answer":"Not necessarily. I tried one of the heads with the Oral B Cross Action 600 but it did not fit properly. When I tried removing it to wash the brush, the head \"broke\" as the fit was too tight","votes":"0","username":"AJ","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Oral b vitality has rotational & oscillation moment. but oral b 2000n has rotating, ossilating & pulsating moment. does this sopport all 3 moment?","answer":"yes of course.","votes":"0","username":"arvind shanbhag","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Age range (description) says kid? is this meant for kid's brush or for the adults alone or for all age groups?","answer":"Perfect for all ages","votes":"0","username":"arvind shanbhag","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it fit Gleem rechargeable toothbrush?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"arvind shanbhag","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used for Gleem rechargeable tooth brush ?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"arvind shanbhag","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067023ff124495ad891f96"},"product_asin":"B07F1NVDZ2","QAs":[{"question":"Is this adjustable","answer":"No, stretchable only, and not good for big heads like me.","votes":"0","username":"Shreyansh G.","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067024ff124495ad891f9d"},"product_asin":"B00JS3PICK","QAs":[{"question":"What is the expiry date??","answer":"2025","votes":"0","username":"Ashirwad seller","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it really takes 1 to 2 months to dispatch","answer":"No it takes up to 7 days upon your location","votes":"0","username":"Ashirwad seller","date":"2022-08-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067025ff124495ad891fa2"},"product_asin":"B07J6PZYF9","QAs":[{"question":"क्या यहां कैमरा है","answer":"It's a action camera holder , not a camera","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep dutta","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या यह कैमरा है","answer":"No, it is just a action camera holder ..","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep dutta","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it fit hero 10?","answer":"Yes it will","votes":"0","username":"Prakhar Gunsola","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fit for gopro hero 9","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Viraj N.","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067026ff124495ad891fac"},"product_asin":"B07PR1CL3S","QAs":[{"question":"Is aqua blue suitable for boys","answer":"Ya absolutely","votes":"0","username":"Bhavesh Trivedi","date":"2022-08-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"boat should launch their mobile phones in market ?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"PRADIP MONDAL","date":"2022-08-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"will it support laptop having Bluetooth connectivity 4.2?","answer":"Please Don't Buy it ye Product bhot kharab hai sound quality bilkul ghatiya hai","votes":"0","username":"Vivek","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Emi me lena h","answer":"Lowda lele mera emi mai","votes":"0","username":"Vivek","date":"2022-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty kya hi","answer":"One year warranty","votes":"0","username":"rash","date":"2022-08-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"whom to contact if my order is not delivered yet?","answer":"If your order is out for delivery Then contact the agent number.","votes":"0","username":"PRADIP MONDAL","date":"2022-08-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"I order this bt my order is cancelled on delivery point I don't cancel","answer":"For details instructions,","votes":"0","username":"PRADIP MONDAL","date":"2022-08-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i increase or decrease the volume using headphones?? Not by touching mobile..!!","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Dakshya Meena","date":"2022-08-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Tracking status not showing","answer":"I think this is an glitch with app.","votes":"0","username":"PRADIP MONDAL","date":"2022-08-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Not getting connected to TV...","answer":"If you have Android TV, then you can check if there is bluetooth version if the TV has bluetooth version then see if you are doing the process properly.","votes":"0","username":"Sudip Das","date":"2022-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty not mentioned anywhere?","answer":"There is a one year warranty with it","votes":"0","username":"mangeshshepal @.","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please available aqua blue colour","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sudip Das","date":"2022-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Charge C type ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"jayesh","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"DeleVari etni late kyu","answer":"Muje bhahat jald mil geya . Sirf 4 days me.","votes":"0","username":"Sudip Das","date":"2022-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aux cable me mic hota hai ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Deepak soni","date":"2022-08-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"With in 6 month any issue happen with headphone can we exchange or replace get","answer":"You can use it's Warranty card for warranty service.","votes":"0","username":"Sudip Das","date":"2022-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which one is good 450 or 450 pro In sound quality?","answer":"Both are same in audio quality just 450 pro have high battery capacity can run longer in full charge","votes":"0","username":"Rohan Sharma","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time taken to chrarge","answer":"2 hour","votes":"0","username":"Diptiben","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is their connect iPhone","answer":"Yes it connectes easily with any smart phone","votes":"0","username":"Debjit Modak","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Chargeing time of boat rockstar 450","answer":"The charging of this headphones is 2- 3 hour","votes":"0","username":"Diptiben","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Difference between 450 and 450 pro","answer":"When not in use, store it in a safe place","votes":"0","username":"PRAJAPATI NILESHKUMAR","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"During stanby mode right side speaker humming sound coming","answer":"It's a defect","votes":"0","username":"Rohan Sharma","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या इस हेडफोन में मेमोरी कार्ड डालकर संगीत सुनने की सुविधा है","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Sanjit K Sinha","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Memorycard slot","answer":"No memory card slot","votes":"0","username":"Pravin chikane","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Memory card","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Rutuj","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the difference between the 450 and 450 pro can you canpare it ??","answer":"Boat rockers 450 pro has a few more options than 450. It is 32grams lighter , 70h playback time new Bluetooth version has usb type c and it is 750mah batery whereas boat rockerz 450 is only 300mah. I use boat rockerz 450 and it is good","votes":"0","username":"JP","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is it that Bluetooth version is not mentioned anywhere in the description?","answer":"It worked ok bt. Version  5.o","votes":"0","username":"PRAJAPATI NILESHKUMAR","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to chrge it","answer":"By dhoop just like JADOO Charged himself from sun","votes":"0","username":"manu","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i return this product?","answer":"Bt version  5.0","votes":"0","username":"PRAJAPATI NILESHKUMAR","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim GST for this product?","answer":"Attached invoice  in your gst return  file.","votes":"0","username":"PRAJAPATI NILESHKUMAR","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"When paired using wire i get sound only from right side and left side i don't get sound","answer":"Check your wire . Whether it is in good or bad condition","votes":"0","username":"Soumya rup shee","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Sir my boat rockerz 450 when wired only right side sound come left side it doesn't work  but when in blootooth i get sound both the side please solve","answer":"It means your cable is defective","votes":"0","username":"P khandelwal","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"yesterday its price was 999 but today it is showing 1299. May i know when the  price will go down again?","answer":"It won't go down anymore only for Amazon prime day offers it will go down","votes":"0","username":"JP","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can  I return this after 2 weeks of delivery?","answer":"No, there is 7 days replacement facility","votes":"0","username":"Sudip Das","date":"2022-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it really good for music and all.... Cause many of the reviews are on a negative side?","answer":"It's totally fine","votes":"0","username":"Dr Rajesh Arora","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I don't want replacement i need refund, what should i do","answer":"I ordered a replacement first time thinking that the one I received was defective but the replacement product had the same issue so I went again for the return/ replacement. This time it didn’t offer a replacement instead gave me the return option.","votes":"0","username":"Ashesha Gupta","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it comes with usb bluetooth adapter to connect with pc which is not bluetooth enabled?","answer":"You will get the ‎boAt Rockerz 450, Charging Cable, User Manual, and Warranty Card. But USB Adaptor is not in the box.","votes":"0","username":"boAt Support","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I bought this headphone 2 days ago. It's working fine. How to register this product for warranty ?","answer":"I have warranty card","votes":"0","username":"Manish","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aux cable lagane pe ek hi side bajata hai kya plz reply","answer":"Koi mechanical issue hoga .","votes":"0","username":"Shobhit kumar","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Iff battery 0 so can i use aux cable","answer":"No charginh cabile","votes":"0","username":"Neerudu venkatesh","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have a question 1year warranty hai ya nhi","answer":"Yes, and I have already exchanged my product 2 times within 7 months.","votes":"0","username":"Amod","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is mic quality ??","answer":"Mic quality is awesome, Noise cancellation is amazing. Sound quality could be little better but it's good as compared to this price range","votes":"0","username":"Amod","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this 450pro","answer":"No , it is boat rockerz 450","votes":"0","username":"Atif Bedar","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its wireless or with wire","answer":"Wire less","votes":"0","username":"Vikas kumar","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I make calls using this earphone when the Bluetooth is on?","answer":"Yes, with the help of the voice assistant inbuilt app.if you have iPhone then - SiriAndroid - Google assistantAlexa can help you anytime.All three assistant can work only if you launch them and use it.see less","votes":"0","username":"Amod","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is headphones is good for calls? I mean does the other person gets the proper voice on call???","answer":"Yeah, voice is good enough","votes":"0","username":"Anand Thakur","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gaming ke liye kesa hai","answer":"I didn't play any game lekin meine yeh dekha hi ki sound quality and battery Back-up dono badiya hai (yani ke 1 number hai)","votes":"0","username":"Siddhant","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is better ? Boat 450 or 600?","answer":"i have brother boat 450 which is running very good battery backup is also good and when down you can also play with 3.5 audio jack chrgin point is type c , just after long running ears start hurting","votes":"0","username":"Bhupendra singh rawat","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it support to lenovo m8 tablet","answer":"Yes it support","votes":"0","username":"Amazon user","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whay battery gets damage after 1year use?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ROYAL TARIQUE","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"When it will come in stock???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ROYAL TARIQUE","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compatible with iPhone XR","answer":"S it's compatible with iOS but i don't have an iOS device with me but used it with my neighbour's","votes":"0","username":"Shamanth P","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Boat rockerz 450  damage ho jaye to","answer":"Bad","votes":"0","username":"Abhi arya","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Headphone have memory card space","answer":"Bad","votes":"0","username":"Abhi arya","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can have 3.5 audio jack in box?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Raj Sahani","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it support Bluetooth version v5.0?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Riya Chaudhary","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"which is the charger cable","answer":"It's kinda magnetic charger you'll have to aline the pin it'll stick automatic likely wireless charge ( they'll provide you charger )","votes":"0","username":"Swapnil","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"have you provided aux cable with this ?","answer":"Yes i have provided but i have to keep product because i have returned it by mistakely,so how can i ?","votes":"0","username":"Raj  ramteke","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Defective product or broken product in condition return facility available or not","answer":"Available","votes":"0","username":"Diwakar","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"63067027ff124495ad891fba"},"product_asin":"B0764MLHRM","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"36 month","votes":"0","username":"RAVEESH. G. K","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"36 month","votes":"0","username":"RAVEESH. G. K","date":"2022-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date","answer":"Nice","votes":"0","username":"patel kelaiya","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please tell expiry and manufacturing date","answer":"4-2022 to 4-2025","votes":"0","username":"RAVEESH. G. K","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry Date?","answer":"36 months from manufacturing date.","votes":"0","username":"Lokesh","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it parabens and sulphates free","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Customer","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Best before use","answer":"36 months from date of mfg","votes":"0","username":"Shashikant D.","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of this product??","answer":"Expiry date of this Product I have purchased is Jan. 2025","votes":"0","username":"Shashikant D.","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Iski expired date kya hai","answer":"Jan. 2025","votes":"0","username":"Shashikant D.","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hlo amazon pay on delivery now should be start","answer":"Yes Pay on delivery is now eligible","votes":"0","username":"Sidharth","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6307c092ff124495ad8ce17d"},"product_asin":"B0B6HNDWYW","QAs":[{"question":"Can this shampoo and conditioner be used for Keratin treated hair?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-08-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"6307c0b5ff124495ad8ce231"},"product_asin":"B09F3RZCZW","QAs":[{"question":"Is the product is of cotton??","answer":"Yes. Very good sweat absorbent","votes":"0","username":"Mousumi","date":"2022-08-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Made up of cotton is it","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mousumi","date":"2022-08-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What material is it made up of?","answer":"Cotton","votes":"0","username":"Mousumi","date":"2022-08-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it durable after washing daily?","answer":"Yes. But I do hand wash not machine wash as it become loose","votes":"0","username":"Mousumi","date":"2022-08-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"630911efff124495ad919f0a"},"product_asin":"B0B6Y7PXTF","QAs":[{"question":"Can i use 6 oil nourish conditioners? after this shampoo","answer":"Yes you can use it","votes":"0","username":"shivi","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use for coloured hair","answer":"No and I suggest u to use shampoo specifically made for colored hair","votes":"0","username":"Sumegha singh…","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it paraben free","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sumegha singh…","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"}]}
